{
    "subject": "resource/Animal_Crossing",
    "predicate": "property/platforms",
    "object": "resource/Wii_U",
    "human_readable": "Animal Crossing is available on Wii U.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9516211748123169,
            "question": "Can you find Animal Crossing on the Wii U?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9300708770751953,
            "question": "Is Animal Crossing a game for the Nintendo Wii U?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6778421998023987,
            "question": "On which gaming console is Animal Crossing available?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4769802689552307,
            "question": "Which console was used to play Animal Crossing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44921958446502686,
            "question": "What gaming platform features Animal Crossing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3913615643978119,
            "question": "What popular Nintendo console hosts Animal Crossing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3588741719722748,
            "question": "Which gaming system released Animal Crossing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.27590087056159973,
            "question": "What game can you play on the Wii U?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2642022967338562,
            "question": "Is Animal Crossing a game for the PlayStation?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.17536219954490662,
            "question": "Name a game available on the Wii U."
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Animal Crossing is available on Wii U.",
            "html": "dbpedia_141_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Animal Crossing a game for the PlayStation?",
            "html": "dbpedia_141_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What game can you play on the Wii U?",
            "html": "dbpedia_141_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which gaming system released Animal Crossing?",
            "html": "dbpedia_141_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_141_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_141_110.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_141_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_141_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_141_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_141_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_141_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_141_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_141_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_141_81.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple \"Animal Crossing is available on Wii U\" based on the provided context information:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this answer is that while the documents mention Animal Crossing being associated with Wii U, they also clarify that it's not a game, but rather an application called Animal Crossing Plaza. This application allows fans to interact and share content related to Animal Crossing, but it's not available as a traditional game on the Wii U console."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly state that Animal Crossing Plaza, which allows the game to be played on the Wii U platform, was announced and is available for download. Therefore, the information supports the statement that Animal Crossing is available on Wii U."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "Animal Crossing Plaza on Wii U is not a game itself, but rather a hub for fans to interact with each other through status updates and screenshots, indicating that the actual Animal Crossing experience is still exclusive to 3DS.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}